http://www.scc.losrios.edu/about-us/our-values/privacy-policy

Skip to Content
Sacramento City College
Why SCC?
Contact Us
Why SCC?
Notifications
Check out remote campus information for students.
Why SCC?
Notifications
Check out remote campus information for students.
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Protecting Privacy and Personal Information
Sacramento City College is committed to protecting personal privacy and the personal information collected via its website. All information you provide to us electronically is kept confidential and will not be applied in ways to which you have not consented.
Encryption and Personal Information
Encryption is used for the transfer of data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result – though we strive to protect your personal information – we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our website. We will not sell or disclose any information that identifies you to a third party.
External users can visit the official Sacramento City College website without revealing any personal information. If you choose to provide us with any personal information, then it will only be used by Sacramento City College to conduct official business. Personal information obtained through the Sacramento City College website will not be disseminated to any unaffiliated third party, except as required by law.
Information Gathering and Use of Cookies
IP Addresses
We use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses (the internet address of your computer) to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. For example, we employ statistical software to identify the parts of our website that are most heavily used. But, we do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable.
Cookies
Like many other websites, portions of our website may use messages given by web browsers to web servers, commonly known as cookies, which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website.
What is a Cookie?
A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer system. This element of data is a piece of text, not a program. The site can only access the information from a cookie sent by the website. We cannot access other cookies sent by other websites or the information contained therein. Additionally, we cannot learn your email address or any other information about you through the use of a cookie. The only way Sacramento City College would learn such information is if you specifically submit that information.
What Does a Cookie Do?
Overall, the use of cookies helps to give you a customized experience while using our website. This information helps us customize our website and allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our website and for what purpose. Through the use of cookies, Sacramento City College will know what is working and what is not. That information is then used to keep our website fresh and relevant to you – the user.
Decline to Accept Cookies
You may decline to accept cookies sent by the website by selecting an option on your browser to reject cookies. Other sites linked to the website may also send cookies; however Sacramento City College does not control such activities. If you decline a cookie, you may not be viewing the website in a way in which it was designed to optimally be presented.
Links to Other Websites
You will encounter links to websites of organizations not directly affiliated with Sacramento City College. Please be aware that Sacramento City College is not responsible for the information practices of external organizations. We recommend you review the privacy policies and/or statements of each website you visit that collects personal information.
Accessibility
We are committed to creating an accessible community – that is, one that provides websites, course materials, documents, and applications that are accessible to all current and future students, faculty, staff, and other constituents. Learn more about our commitment to accessibility.
Our Values
Student Rights and Responsibilities
Academic Rights and Responsibilities
Access to Student Information (FERPA)
Disability Services and Programs for Students (DSPS)
